BEN KALSKY

UX DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Experienced Product Owner with a demonstrated history of working in the interactive media industry. Skilled in UX principles and UI design methods. Strong arts and design professional graduated from Avni Institute of Art and Design.

CONTACT

ADDRESS

Azor, Israel

PHONE

+972-528816959

EMAIL

benkalsky@gmail.com

WEBSITE

http://benkalsky.com









HOBBY

Coffee, Beatch, Photography, Traveling the World and eating great food :)

EXPERIENCE

2007-2018 Freelance

UX Developer & Consultant

Dome9 Security 2017-2018

UX Engineer

Apester 2014-2017

Creative Director

EDUCATION

2010-2014 **Avni Institute of Art &**

Design

Interactive Media Design

Israel Defense Forces 2002-2005

Professional Photography

Boyer High School 1996-2002

Biology & Music

SKILLS

UX, UI, Prototyping, Interaction, Web, Graphic Design, Typography, Web Development, Branding & Identity, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Angular.js, WordPress, Photography, After Effects, Vector Illustration, jQuery, JavaScript, Start-ups, Entrepreneurship